John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1938-2000; 60 linear feet
  - Campbell, Donald, 1960-1968; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Janet, 1977; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Paul J., 1976; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Stewart F., 1993-1994; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Vincent N., 1977; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Wilfred E., 1951-1952; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Canby, Edward Tatnall, 1912-, 1939-1973; 47 items (Box 6)
  - Cannon, Edward W., 1967-1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cannon, Robert, 1977-1980; 10 items (Box 6)
  - Capobiance, Michael F., 1979; 8 items (Box 6)
  - Card, Stuart L., 1986; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Carey, Howard, 1951; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Carlson, Edward, 1965; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Carlson, Walter M., 1965; 2 item (Box 6)
  - Carlton, M. Barry, 1953; 2 item (Box 6)
  - Carlyle, J., 1966; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Carmichael, Leonard, 1956; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1963-1988; 10 items (Box 6)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1971-1974; 8 items (Box 6)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University - Statistics Advisory Board, 1992-1993; 15 items (Box 6)
  - Carney, John B., 1977-1980; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Carr, M. B., 1978; 5 item (Box 6)
  - Carrillo, Rene, 1965; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Carroll, Cliff, 1985; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Carroll, J. Douglas, 1969-1983; 8 items (Box 6)
  - Carroll, Sarah, 1954-1956; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Carter, Herbert E., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Case Institute of Technolog - Operations Research Group, 1957-1962; 19 items (Box 6)
  - Case Institute of Technology - Visiting Committee Department of Mathematics, 1962-1968; 14 items (Box 6)
  - Catalano, Paul, 1993; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Stanford, Calif.), 1978-1983; Folder 1 (Box 6)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Stanford, Calif.), 1986-1994; Folder 2 (Box 6)
  - Center for Environmental Studies, 1974-1976; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Center for Institutional Differences Study, 1974-1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Central Intelligence Agency - U2 Program, 1954-1994; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Cetron Electronic Corporation, 1961; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Chacko, George Kuttickal, 1930-?, n.d.; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Chambers, John, 1965-1982; 10 items (Box 6)
  - Chand, Uttam, 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Chandra, Jagdish, 1988-1994; 38 items (Box 6)
  - Chandrasekhar, S., 1953-1970; 9 items (Box 6)
  - Changnon, Stanley Alcide, 1985; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Chanmugam, Rajan, 1961; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Chao, Min-Te, 1986; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Chapman, A. B., 1952; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Chapple, Eliot Dismore, 1969; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Chase, Leslie, 1961; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Chatfield, C., 1985; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Chatterjee, S., 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Chauncey, Henry, 1968-1992; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Chayes, Felix, 1954-1970; 10 items (Box 6)
  - Chemicals and Health, 1972-1974; Folder 1 (Box 6)
  - Chemicals and Health, 1981; Folder 2 (Box 6)
  - Chernoff, Herman, 1960-1988; 25 items (Box 6)
  - Chervin, Robert, 1979; 11 items (Box 6)
  - Chess, 1973-1975; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Chiang, Chin Long, 1915-?, 1961-1985; 10 items (Box 6)
  - Childers, Donald G., 1977-1982; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Childers, James S., 1899-?, 1963-1965; Folder 1 (Box 6)
  - Childers, James S., 1899-?, n.d.; Folder 2 (Box 6)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 1928, 1959; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Christ, Carl F., 1953-1976; 11 items (Box 6)
  - Chromatography, 1943-1946; Folder 1 (Box 6)
  - Chromatography, n.d.; Folder 2 (Box 6)
  - Church, Russell, 1978-1984; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Chynoweth, Alan, 1979; 1 item (Box 6)
  - CIBA-GEIGY Corporation, 1980-1989; 12 items (Box 6)
  - Ciminera, Joseph, 1949-1975; Folder 1 (Box 7)
  - Ciminera, Joseph, 1976-1980; Folder 2 (Box 7)
  - Ciminera, Joseph, 1981-1985; Folder 3 (Box 7)
  - Ciminera, Joseph, 1986-1992; Folder 4 (Box 6)
  - Circle Fitting, 1956; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Circuit Ideas, 1939; 15 items (Box 7)
  - Citation Index, 1964-1974; 12 items (Box 7)
  - Citizens' Commission on Science, Law and the Food Supply, 1973-1974; 15 items (Box 7)
  - Citron, Robert R., 1961; 9 items (Box 7)
  - Clapp, Verner W., 1961-1962; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Clarahan, Charles H., 1954; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Claringbold, Peter J., 1971; Folder 1 (Box 7)
  - Claringbold, Peter J., 1972; Folder 2 (Box 7)
  - Claringbold, Peter J., 1973-1979; Folder 3 (Box 7)
  - Clark, A. N., 1950-1959; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Clark, Leslie L., 1959-1960; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Clark, Nancy, 1981-1986; Folder 1 (Box 7)
  - Clark, Nancy, 1987; Folder 2 (Box 7)
  - Clark, Nancy, 1988-1989; Folder 3 (Box 7)
  - Clark, R. Malcolm, 1978-1979; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Clark, William, 1985; 11 items (Box 7)
  - Clarke, Larry, 1988; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Clarkson, James A., 1952-1955; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Clatworthy, William H., 1955-1957; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Clements, Cleveland W., 1968; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Cleveland, Harlan, 1965-1979; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Cleveland, William S, 1943-, 1980-1992; 25 items (Box 7)
  - Cleverdon, Cyril W., 1960-1966; 18 items (Box 7)
  - Clewlow, R. H., 1968; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Clifford, Paul, 1955-1971; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Climate Impact Committee, 1976; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Clogston, A. M., 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Cochran, William Gemmell, 1909-, 1946-1959; Folder 1 (Box 7)
  - Cochran, William Gemmell, 1909-, 1961-1981; Folder 2 (Box 7)
  - Cochrane, Archibold L., 1949-1977; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, A. Clifford, 1950-1971; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Aaron, 1935-?, 1990; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, E. Richard, 1953; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Leon W., 1955-1972; 10 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Michael, 1981-1992; 30 items (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Reuben, 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Cohn, Ernst, 1966; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Cohn, Harry, 1980-1983; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Cohn, Harvey, 1958-1961; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Cole, Randal H., 1949-1956; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Cole, William G., 1988; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Coleman, Howard, 1966-1968; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Coleman, James S., 1964-1969; 16 items (Box 7)
  - Coleman, John J., 1958; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Coleman, John S., 1968-1971; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Collbohm, Frank R., 1947; 13 items (Box 7)
  - Collier, Albert, 1961; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Collier, Simon, 1953-1955; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Collins, James R., 1971; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Colorado State, 1969-1983; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Columbia University, 1978-1986; 13 items (Box 7)
  - Comisky, Jim, 1958; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Committee on the International Exchange of Persons, 1966-1969; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Committee on Mathematical Physics, 1947; 14 items (Box 7)
  - Committee on Project Research, n.d.; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China, 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Program in Mathematics, 1968; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Computer Science Education Conference Report, 1970; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Computer, 1965-1971; Folder 1 (Box 7)
  - Computer, 1977-1979; Folder 2 (Box 7)
  - Computing Arrangement, 1955-1963; 15 items (Box 7)
  - Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences, 1963; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Conference material, 1948-1949; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Conference on Critical Evaluation of Chemical and Physical Structural Information, Dartmouth College, 1973, 1972; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Conference on Critical Evaluation of Chemical and Physical Structural Information, Dartmouth College, 1973, 1973-1974; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Conference on Electronic Information Handling (2nd: 1967: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania), 1966-1967; 11 items (Box 8)
  - Conference on Frontiers of Educational Measure and Information Systems, 1973; 10 items (Box 8)
  - Conference on Statistics and Anthropology, 1965; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Conference on the Design of Experiments in Army Research, Development, and Testing, 1986-1988; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Conrad, George T., 1954; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Conrad, Miles G., 1961; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Conservation Foundation, The, 1968-1970; 15 items (Box 8)
  - Conservation Foundation, The - Draft manuscript and comments., 1969; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Consolazio, William V., 1953; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Contaminated, 1945-1947; 7 items (Box 8)
  - Cooley, James W., 1964-1993; 27 items (Box 8)
  - Coombs, Clyde Hamilton, 1912-?, 1960-1964; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Cooper, K. W., 1955; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cornell, John A., 1982; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Corner, George W., 1963-1978; 20 items (Box 8)
  - Cornfield, Jerome, 1949-1955; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cornfield, Jerome, 1956-1977; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Cornish, Edmund Alfred, 1957-1968; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Corwin, Thomas, 1972-1973; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Cosmos Club, 1955 1969; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cosmos Club, 1976-1991; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Costigan-Eaves, Patricia, 1988; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Court, Arnold, 1972; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Courtney-Pratt, J. S., 1959-1965; 22 items (Box 8)
  - Cover, Thomas, 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cox, David R., 1955-1979; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cox, David R., 1981-1993; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Cox, Gertrude M., 1946-1952; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cox, Gertude M., 1953-1957; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Cox, Nicholas J., 1972-1993; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Cox, William M., 1987; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Coxeter, H. S. M., 1953-1954; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Coyne, J. Patrick, 1963-1967; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Craig, Cecil, 1956-1960; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cramer, Elliot, 1978; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Cramer, Harald, 1964-1972; 7 items (Box 8)
  - Crampton, Theodore H. M., 1956-1957; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Crandall, Charles B., 1953; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Crandall, Robert H., 1976; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Crawford, Bryce, 1973-1980; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Cressie, Noel, 1975-1986; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cressie, Noel, 1987-1988; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Crocker, Stephen, 1966; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Crombie, D. S., 1955; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Crommelin, R. D., 1965; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cronback, Lee J., 1966-1979; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Cross, Joseph K., 1965; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Crow, Edwin L., 1961-1985; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Crow, James F., 1952-1975; 11 items (Box 8)
  - Crowley, Thomas H., 1965-1967; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Crump, S. Lee, 1950-1958; 17 items (Box 8)
  - Crutcher, Harold L., 1958-1959; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Culbertson, J. E., 1955-1956; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cureton, Edward Eugene, 1902-, 1950-1955; Folder 1 (Box 8)
  - Cureton, Edward Eugene, 1902-, 1956-1970; Folder 2 (Box 8)
  - Cureton, Theodore, 1950; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Curnow, R. N., 1964; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Current, James, 1960; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Curtis, P. C., 1973-1974; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Curtiss, John H., 1953-1956; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Cutkomp, Laurence K., 1965; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cutler, C. C., 1961-1963; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cutler, Preston S., 1958-1978; 7 items (Box 8)
  - Cziffra, Peter, 1979-1982; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Dachs, J. Norberto, 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Daddario, Emilio, 1974; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Daedalus, 1987-1988; 14 items (Box 8)
  - Dagum, Estele B., 1979; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Dahrendorf, Ralf, 1964-1966; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Dalal, Sid, n.d.; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Dale, Michael B., 1968-1980; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Dalenius, Tore, 1967; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Dalgleish, Lenard I., 1989-1992; 14 items (Box 8)
  - Daly, Joseph F., 1951; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Dancis, Joseph, 1950; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Daniel, Cuthbert, 1950-1993; 44 items (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Henry E., 1953-1956; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Dantzig, George B., 1962-1972; 6 items (Box 8)
  - Darling, Don A., 1952; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Darling, Frank, 1969; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Darling, Paul G., 1952-1953; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Darlington, D., 1954; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Data Analysis Seminar, 1962; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Datatrol Corporation, 1964; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Datta, P. R., 1960; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Daus, Paul, 1944; 1 item (Box 9)
  - David, Edward, 1958-1979; 26 items (Box 9)
  - David, Henry, 1969-1973; 6 items (Box 9)
  - David, Herbert A., 1962-1994; 33 items (Box 9)
  - David, Herbert T., 1956-1968; 9 items (Box 9)
  - David, Martin, 1989; 3 items (Box 9)
  - David, Nancy, 1973-1978; 13 items (Box 9)
  - Davidson, C., 1955-1958; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Davidson, J. H., 1952-1956; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Davies, P. L., 1993; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Davis, Philip, 1970-1984; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Davis, Ruth, 1986; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Davis, William H., 1951; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Dawson, Jay W., 1976; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Day, Besse B., 1948-1951; 15 items (Box 9)
  - Day, Willard F., 1952; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Dayhoff, Eugene, 1962; 1 item (Box 9)
  - de Beer, Edwin, 1945-1950; 11 items (Box 9)
  - Deason, Hilary J., 1955; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Deaton, Eric, 1979; 2 items (Box 9)
  - DeBaun, Robert M., 1969-1980; 8 items (Box 9)
  - Decker, Fred W., 1963; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Dees, Bowen C., 1955-1966; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Deevey, Edward S., 1950; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Defense, 1951-1956; 11 items (Box 9)
  - DeGroot, Morris, 1986-1987; 7 items (Box 9)
  - Deken, Joseph, 1977-1985; 29 items (Box 9)
  - Dekker, Marcel, 1978-1992; 5 items (Box 9)
  - DeLacy, Ian, 1990; 12 items (Box 9)
  - Delate, E. J., 1952-1955; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Delfiner, Pierre, 1977-1981; 3 items (Box 9)
  - DeLong, Greta, 1957; 5 items (Box 9)
  - DeLury, Daniel B., 1948-1955; 7 items (Box 9)
  - Deming, W. Edwards (William Edwards), 1900-, 1945-1953; Folder 1 (Box 9)
  - Deming, W. Edwards (William Edwards), 1900-, 1954-1992; Folder 2 (Box 9)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland, 1929-, 1955-1985; 20 items (Box 9)
  - Dempster, Everett R., 1975; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Densen Paul, 1950-1971; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Dershowitz, Arthur F., 1954-1959; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Deshpande, Jayant V., 1967; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Devereux, R. A., 1962; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Dewey, Edward, 1956-1957; 9 items (Box 9)
  - Dews, Peter, 1985; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Diaconis, Persi, 1980-1983; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Dicke, Robert H., 1977; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Dietzold, Robert L., 1973; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Diment, William, 1960; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Divgi, D. R., 1991; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Dix, Robert K., 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Dix, William S., 1956-1969; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Dixon, Wilfrid Joseph, 1915-, 1951-1963; Folder 1 (Box 9)
  - Dixon, Wilfrid Joseph, 1915-, 1964-1966; Folder 2 (Box 9)
  - Dixon, Wilfrid Joseph, 1915-, 1967-1977; Folder 3 (Box 9)
  - Dobriner, Konrad, 1949-1951; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Dodd, Stuart, 1947-1959; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Dodds, H. W., 1955; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Dodge, Harold French, 1893-, 1952-1979; 23 items (Box 9)
  - Doherty, William H., 1957-1982; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Doig, Alison, 1965; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Dolby, James L., 1954-1968; Folder 1 (Box 9)
  - Dolby, James L., 1970-1985; Folder 2 (Box 9)
  - Dolph, Charles L., 1940-1963; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Donoho, David L., 1970-1982; Folder 1 (Box 9)
  - Donoho, David L., 1983-1984; Folder 2 (Box 9)
  - Donoho, David L., 1985-1989; Folder 3 (Box 9)
  - Donoho, David L., 1990-1993; Folder 4 (Box 9)
  - Donoho, David L., n.d.; Folder 5 (Box 9)
  - Doob, Joseph L., 1946-1959; 11 items (Box 9)
  - Doob, Leonard William, 1909-?, 1954; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Dorn, Harold Fred, 1906-1963, 1951-1958; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Douglas, J. B., 1961-1985; 48 items (Box 9)
  - Douglas, Roy, 1980-1981; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1961-1971; Folder 1 (Box 9)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1972-1974; Folder 2 (Box 9)
  - Dowker, Clifford Hugh, 1912-?, 1938; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Downs, Florence S., 1981; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Downton, F., 1966-1968; 8 items (Box 9)
  - Doyle, Lauren B., 1926-?, 1966; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Draeger, A. A., 1953; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Draft, n.d.; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Draper, David, 1987-1993; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Draper, John F., 1972; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Draper, Norman Richard, 1968-1979; 8 items (Box 9)
  - Drenick, R. F., 1955; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Dressel, F. G., 1956-1972; 20 items (Box 9)
  - Dromey, R.G., 1973; 7 items (Box 9)
  - DuBois, Philip H., (Philip Hunter), 1903-?, 1972; 2 items (Box 9)
  - DuBridge, Lee A. (Lee Alvin), 1901-?, 1969; 11 items (Box 9)
  - Duckworth, W. E. (Walter Eric), 1958; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Duke Mathematical Journal, 1941-1950; 92 items (Box 10)
  - DuMond, Jesse W., 1953-1959; 11 items (Box 10)
  - DuMouchel, William Hermas, 1982-1983; Folder 1 (Box 10)
  - DuMouchel, William Hermas, 1987; Folder 2 (Box 10)
  - Duncan, Acheson J. (Acheson Johnston), 1904-?, 1947-1955; 39 items (Box 10)
  - Duncan, David B., 1946-1954; 39 items (Box 10)
  - Duncan, George T., 1976-1982; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Duncan, K. A. (Karen A.), 1980; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Dunne, John, 1953; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Dunnett, Charles W., 1951-1991; 20 items (Box 10)
  - DuPont, 1977; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Durbin, James, 1961-1984; 16 items (Box 10)
  - Dwyer, Paul S. (Paul Sumner), 1901-?, 1948-1965; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Dyke, H. Gordon, 1951; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Earle, Albert P., 1949; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Easterling, Robert G., 1964-1977; 9 items (Box 10)
  - Eastern Psychological Association Meeting. Atlantic City, 1947, 1946-1947; 6 items (Box 10)
  - Easton, George, 1983-1987; Folder 1 (Box 10)
  - Easton, George, 1988; Folder 2 (Box 10)
  - Easton, George, 1989; Folder 3 (Box 10)
  - Easton, George, 1993-1994; Folder 4 (Box 10)
  - Eaton, William W., 1967; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Eckler, Albert, 1951-1973; 15 items (Box 10)
  - Ecometric Society, 1949; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Econometric Society, 1948-1952; 10 items (Box 10)
  - Econometrika, 1948-1952; 16 items (Box 10)
  - Eddy, William F., 1971-1992; 18 items (Box 10)
  - Eden, Murray, 1958; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Edmonds, Francis C., 1964; 6 items (Box 10)
  - Education of a Generalist, 1948-1949; 10 items (Box 10)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1954-1991; 21 items (Box 10)
  - Edwards, George D., 1947-1949; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Efron, Bradley, 1984-1991; 11 items (Box 10)
  - Egler, Frank, 1950-1965; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Egner, Frank, 1953; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Ehrenberg, Andrew S. C., 1979-1982; Folder 1 (Box 10)
  - Ehrenberg, Andrew S. C., 1983-1984; Folder 2 (Box 10)
  - Ehrenberg, Andrew S. C., 1988-1993; Folder 3 (Box 10)
  - Eilenberg, Samuel, 1940-1948; 10 items (Box 10)
  - Eisenberg, Murray, 1973; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Eisenhart, Churchill, 1948-1957; Folder 1 (Box 10)
  - Eisenhart, Churchill, 1960-1980; Folder 2 (Box 10)
  - Eisenhart, L. P., 1951; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Eisenman, Richard, 1975; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Elashoff, Robert, 1965-1973; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Elder, Joseph D., 1955; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Eldredge, G. G., 1945; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Electric punched card accounting machinces, 1940-1946; 4 items (Box 10)
  - Elliott, Emerson J., 1989; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Ellis, William, 198-1992; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Elveback, Lila, 1965; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Elvers, Eva, 1975; 5 items (Box 10)
  - Emerson, John D., 1981-1991; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1963-1965; 22 items (Box 10)
  - Encyclopedia of Mathematics and its Applications, 1974-1975; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Engel, Eduardo, M.R.A., 1989; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Environmenal Protection Agency, 1971-1974; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Ericksen, Eugene Pennell, 1970-1989; Folder 1 (Box 10)
  - Ericksen, Eugene Pennell, 1990-1991; Folder 2 (Box 10)
  - Erickson, Bonnie H., 1976; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Ericson, William Arnold, 1934-?, 1969-1977; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Esso Research and Engineering Company, 1955-1963; 10 items (Box 10)
  - Evans, D. A., 1972; 1 items (Box 10)
  - Evans, David H., 1924-?, 1968-1980; 12 items (Box 11)
  - Evans, Elizabeth, 1978; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Evans, Ian S., 1979; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Evans, William, 1971; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Exploratory Committee on Assessing Progress in Education, 1965-1966; Folder 1 (Box 11)
  - Exploratory Committee on Assessing Progress in Education, 1968-1969; Folder 2 (Box 11)
  - Exploratory Data Analysis Revisions, 1971-1972; 17 items (Box 11)
  - Exxon Research and Engineering Company, 1979-1981; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Eyland, Ann, 1979-1980; 9 items (Box 11)
  - Fager, E. W., 1958; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Fairbairn, H. W. (Harold Williams), 1906-?, 1952-1954; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Fairthorne, Robert Arthur, 1967; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Fano, Robert M., 1959; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Fay, Robert, 1991; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Feder, Paul I., 1974; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Federal Statistics Users' Conference, 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1948-1950; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Federer, Walter Theodore, 1915-?, 1948-1978; Folder 1 (Box 11)
  - Federer, Walter Theodore, 1915-?, n.d.; Folder 2 (Box 11)
  - Feinleib, Manning, 1935-?, 1958; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Feinstein, Alvan R., 1925-?, 1978-1981; 11 items (Box 11)
  - Feldmesser, Robert, 1973; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Feller, Clara N., 1963-1968; 54 items (Box 11)
  - Feller, William, 1906-1907, 1940-1961; 25 items (Box 11)
  - Fellow surveys, n.d.; 18 items (Box 11)
  - Ferguson, Thomas, 1958-1961; 13 items (Box 11)
  - Ferris, Benjamin G., 1976-1985; Folder 1 (Box 11)
  - Ferris, Benjamin G., 1986-1987; Folder 2 (Box 11)
  - Fertig, John W., 1950; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Ficken, Fred A., 1963-1971; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Field, Christopher, 1996; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Fienberg, Stephen, 1970-1989; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Figueroa, Jeanette, 1988-1990; 7 items (Box 11)
  - Filliben, James, 1974-1990; 11 items (Box 11)
  - Finch, Steve, 1967-1977; 14 items (Box 11)
  - Findley, David, 1979-1978; 7 items (Box 11)
  - Finger, Harold, 1969; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Finley, Carmen J., 1968; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Finney, David J., 1949-1979; 12 items (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Nick I., 1978-1980; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Robert, 1971; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer, Sir, 1890-1962, 1946-1952; Folder 1 (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer, Sir, 1890-1962, 1953-1956; Folder 2 (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer, Sir, 1890-1962 - Guide, 1948-1949; 19 items (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Walter D., 1953; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Fisherkeller, Mary Anne, 1972-1978; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Fisk, James B., 1957-1966; 14 items (Box 11)
  - Flagg, J. F., 1939-1940; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Flanagan, J. L., 1961-1964; 11 items (Box 11)
  - Flesch, Rudolf, 1950; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Flexagons, 1955-1956; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Flinn, Edward A., 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Flood, Merrill Meeks, 1908-, 1945-1961; Folder 1 (Box 11)
  - Flood, Merrill Meeks, 1908-, 1962-1981; Folder 2 (Box 11)
  - Flores, Ana Maria, 1966-1968; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Florida State University, 1966-1967; 14 items (Box 11)
  - Fluid Dynamics Symposium, 1946-1947; 9 items (Box 11)
  - Folk Dancing, 1946-1950; 43 items (Box 11)
  - Folkers, Karl, 1955-1956; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Follettie, Joseph, 1986; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Foote, Paul, 1957-1971; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Forrester, Jay W., 1953; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Forsythe, George, 1950-1966; 10 items (Box 11)
  - Foster, Ronald M., 1942-1958; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Foster, Walter D., 1950-1955; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Fowlkers, Edward B., 1981-1982; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Fox, A. H., 1951; 2items (Box 11)
  - Frank, Leonard, 1960; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Frankel, Sidney, 1952; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Franklin, N. L., 1951; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Fraser, Donald A. S., 1947-1968; 44 items (Box 11)
  - Frederiksen, Norman, 1955-1963; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Freedman, David, 1960--1983; 7 items (Box 11)
  - Freedman, Laurence S., 1991-1992; 10 items (Box 11)
  - Freeland, Howard, 1977; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Freeman, Harold A., 1949-1955; 9 items (Box 12)
  - Freeman, John, 1951-1953; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Freibarger, Walter, 1959-1993; 13 items (Box 12)
  - Frenkiel, Francois N., 1952-1960; 7 items (Box 12)
  - Freund, Richard, 1954; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Friedlander, Gerhart, 1979; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Friedman, David H., 1982; 7 items (Box 12)
  - Friedman, J. H. (Jerome H.), 1972-1980; Folder 1 (Box 12)
  - Friedman, J. H. (Jerome H.), 1981; Folder 2 (Box 12)
  - Friedman, J. H. (Jerome H.), 1981; Folder 3 (Box 12)
  - Friedman, J. H. (Jerome H.), 1982-1993; Folder 4 (Box 12)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1912-?, 1958-1959; 6 items (Box 12)